So great to see all of you.
Very good to be home.
It is incredible how large our ecosystem
in Taiwan has become. Most of the time
when people think about ecosystem, they
think about our software stack. They
think about the developer ecosystem
above the computing systems that NVIDIA
builds.
But NVIDIA's ecosystem
spans all the way upstream to all of our
supply chain
here in Taiwan where it all begins and
downstream all the way to data centers
and eventually to end users. Today,
we're going to talk about almost all of
the ecosystem. There's so many people to
thank. I love my ecosystem here.
I mean, there's so many companies here
and some of my favorite ecosystem
partners.
So many.
Taiwan's rich ecosystem.
The richest ecosystem, the world's best
supply chain ecosystem. Unbelievable.
Two years ago when I was here, I started
to talk to you about how AI has moved
from generative AI and the other waves
of AIs that are coming. The next wave of
AI was agentic AI.
And today, we can say that agentic AI
has arrived, that useful AI has arrived.
Now, what does that mean from the
industry's perspective?
From the industry's perspective, that
means that tokens are now in
extraordinary demand. Because if you
could do this, you're going to want to
produce more of it. And because tokens
are now profitable units,
tokens are now profitable
units of revenues.
Because it is now profitable, the AI
companies want to build a lot more
tokens, generate a lot more tokens,
build more AI factories, which is the
reason why compute demand here in Taiwan
has skyrocketed.
It is precisely the reason why all of
you are so busy and your businesses are
doing so well. In fact, that looks like
some of your stock price.
The compute pattern has changed.
Everything has changed. So,
the first idea is that useful AI has
arrived. AI is now a profit generator.
AI is now a GDP generator. And behind it
is a whole new kind of computing
pattern. Not just a large language
model, but an agent. Today,
almost everything we're going to talk
about is going to be based on this. So,
let me take a quick moment and show you
what I'm talking about. Inside
in this is a this is an agent. It's an
agent application.
In the old days, this would be
application.
This would be code.
And this would be operating system.
Application, code running inside an
application inside an operating system.
Today, it is agent, which consists of a
large language model or many
sitting inside a harness. And that
harness helps it orchestrates it to do
productive work.
This is the input. When that input
comes,
it has to understand, observe, reason,
act, use tools,
use tools. That tool could be a
spreadsheet, web browser, a data
processing engine, database engine, for
example.
This
is orchestrated this harness orchestrate
this
routing of information every single time
it touches either processing the context
understanding what is happening
reasoning about what to do
coming up with a plan that you can act
that it acts on. That orchestration path
is orchestrated by some software.
And so this is fundamentally a agent. It
deals with short-term memory
called working memory, long-term memory,
just like we do, we have long-term
memory. And so the memory management
system is incredibly important. This
entire system is called an agent. The
large language model
is used to do the thinking
and the harness
connects everything together, just like
an operating system.
Okay? And so this is the new computing
model, and this is what an agent. It
could do incredible things. This is the
big breakthrough.
The simultaneous convert the convergence
of large language models that are now
able to
do a really good job thinking,
reasoning, planning, using tools and the
fact that we have now these harnesses
that manages memory, the orchestration
uses tools, we can now do amazing
things.
>> We built our next generation
Vera Rubin.
Vera Rubin is not one chip.
Vera Rubin is not a GPU only. It starts
with a GPU,
but Vera Rubin is incredible.
This entire thing is Vera Rubin
from end to end.
It has GPUs,
Vera Rubin NVLink 72.
It is orchestrated by Vera CPUs I'm
going to tell you more about. The
storage systems
revolutionary. Vera, along with CX 9,
our software stack called Doka,
the security processor that's inside so
that everything is encrypted
at rest,
in motion,
as well as in use.
Everything across this is secure because
the AI model is so precious.
This is the reason why this entire
system
obeys confidential computing.
Each one of these systems would be a
complete revolution in itself.
Vera Rubin is the most ambitious
endeavor in the history of our company.
The whole company worked on Vera Rubin
across all 40,000 engineers, not to
mention all of you.
All of you participated in the creation
of this entire system. Vera Rubin
is really a miracle, and it's not just
one chip, it is so many.
Well, it's even beyond that.
A long time ago, Nvidia used to be a GPU
company.
But, over the years, we've evolved
to become a systems company. You're
looking here now for the most complex
systems, most complex and ground-up
system ever designed.
But, ultimately, our customers, our
partners
don't want to buy computers.
They want to build AI factories, which
is the reason why Nvidia has really
started to transform ourselves yet
again.
You could see so much of our technology
is now at the entire infrastructure
scale.
Our partners are at infrastructure
Power generators, cooling systems, the
grid providers.
So many
industrial companies are now part of our
ecosystem because ultimately, we're
trying to build an entire stack just
like GPUs, just like when we were
building Grace Blackwell NVLink 72, just
like now
we are building a full-stack system so
that
our customers could build amazing AI
infrastructure. Now, doing this well
and becoming incredibly good at at
helping customers build AI factories and
deploying AI factories is incredibly
important and the reason for that is
this.
Compute is revenue now.
Compute is profit.
The absence of revenues and profit is
loss.
And so it's really important to realize
that this is when this is an example of
an AI infrastructure coming online.
It could take
it could be coming online quickly. It
could take a while.
It's throughput could be high, it could
be low.
It's resilience and reliability could be
good or bad.
And its lifetime of usefulness could be
long or short.
Because this represents
50, 60, going to a hundred billion
dollars.
This curve matters greatly.
Which is the reason why Nvidia is such a
great partner working with us because of
our
fully integrated capability.
We didn't just come up with a PowerPoint
slide.
We created the entire infrastructure. We
connected everything together. We built
out billions and billions of it
ourselves
to make sure that everything works well.
As a result of that, our time
our time to first token, our time to
first token, our time to first inference
our time
to training turned on
is much faster.
Second, because our
throughput per watt, our tokens per watt
is utterly world-class.
And the reason for that is because we
integrate everything. We design
everything from the ground up. We
simulate the entire system and we use
extreme co-design. Just like I showed
you just now with the Vera Rubin rack,
everything was designed in order to
deliver on this incredible throughput.
If your data center, if your factory has
1 gigawatt,
it will not have more.
1 gigawatt means 1 gigawatt.
That's all the power generation you
could do.
If you have 1 gigawatt of power, then
throughput per watt is revenues because
every token is profitable.
Every token is revenues.
This is the future.
Compute is revenues. Performance per
watt is your revenues. Choosing the
wrong architecture
just because the chips are cheaper
doesn't translate.
Doesn't make sense.
You need to make sure that your revenues
per watt
the more you buy, the
more you make.
Here I am standing in front of you.
Vera Rubin is in full production.
It the the supply chain we created for
Vera Rubin is twice as large as Grace
Blackwell.
Not Yeah, it's incredible. And And
what used to take 2 hours
to assemble one Grace Blackwell rack now
only takes 5 minutes.
So, not only is the capacity higher, the
throughput is a lot faster.
And we need it all to support the
demand.
This ecosystem is extraordinary.
Millions of square feet has been put
online to support Grace Blackwell and
preparing now, ramping up now, Vera
Rubin. I want to thank all of you. Vera
Rubin is now in full production. Thank
you.
Ladies and gentlemen, Vera Rubin.
Vera Rubin
was not just built for AI.
AI Vera Rubin was not built just to run
AI. Vera Rubin was built to run agents.
This is an agentic system. Imagine the
complexity.
Which is the reason why agents is the
last
computer science breakthrough. It has
taken this many years for agents to
realize its potential and become useful.
It stands to reason that the computer
that runs it is the most advanced in the
world. This is Vera Rubin. Let's take a
look. Can we bring out Vera Rubin,
please?
This is This is Vera Rubin. Vera Rubin
NVLink 72.
This is the Grock LPX. At the next GTC,
I'm going to talk to you about a lot
more of this. Today, we have so much to
talk to you about.
This is
Vera CPU rack. 256
CPUs, all liquid cooled. Let me tell you
about Vera in just a moment. This is the
Vera BlueField storage
processing system and also security
system. And of course, this is our
Mellanox networking, the world's first
CPO.
This is Vera Rubin. Incredible
technology all coming together.
Now, when we built When we built Hopper,
we built Hopper, as you know, for
pre-training.
Pre-training was the most important
application, the most important workload
we were working on at the time.
Then when we worked on Grace Blackwell,
everybody said, "Jensen, you know,
Nvidia is really good at pre-training.
Inference is so easy. Do you remember
that?"
People used to say, "Inference is so
easy. We could do that, too."
But as you know, inference equals money.
And the models, MOEs, are so
complicated. And to do it at incredibly
high
response time,
fast interactivity, and high throughput
at the same time is incredibly hard.
Which is the reason why we created
NVLink 72.
Today, NVIDIA's token cost is the lowest
in the world. Not by 10%, by X factors,
orders of magnitude.
All because we did extreme co-design.
All because we understood the computing
model, the computing pattern of
inference,
and we were able to create NVLink 72.
Now,
with Vera Rubin,
it is beyond inference. It is now
inference in an agentic agentic system.
This is
Vera Rubin.
No cables,
no hoses, no fans.
What used to take, the last time when I
showed this to you, we had cables
everywhere.
Vera CPUs,
CPUs built for the age of AI.
All of the CPUs until now
were created for people.
We were the users.
We were the users, we were the renters.
The way we use CPUs, we live in a world
counted by seconds.
The way we rent CPUs in the cloud,
each one of them, more you can more CPU
cores you have, the more you can rent.
The economics of the old the use case of
the old CPU and the economics of the old
CPU fundamentally different than agents.
Agents
are impatient.
They don't live in a world that is in
seconds, they live in a world that's in
nanoseconds.
When it uses a tool,
it wants the response time to be as fast
as possible.
When it access database, it has to come
back as soon as possible.
Every moment that the agent is waiting
keeps it from going to the next step,
the next step, the next step.
It is vital
that we make the CPUs
as low latency as possible, as
interactive as possible.
So, we created Vera CPU for the age of
AI.
Now, inside our system, it's used for
three different ways. The first way, of
course, is Vera Rubin
for thinking.
And inside the Vera Rubin rack, there
already two CPUs.
As you know, we are building and selling
millions
of Vera Rubins. We have sold millions of
Grace Blackwells. Nvidia already is one
of the largest CPU makers in the world.
Vera In the Vera Rubin rack are two
CPUs.
One
for orchestrating and managing the GPUs,
managing the KV cache,
dealing with all of the software that
runs in the rack. We also have the Grace
Bluefield that is used for security and
isolation.
The Vera compute
is used for the harness, the
orchestration of the AI models, tool
use, accessing the database.
And the data servers
are right here, Vera Bluefield. The
fastest storage fastest storage servers,
the fastest storage system the world has
ever made. And the reason why this is so
vital
is because agents are accessing memory,
accessing memory so
fast.
These systems
the storage server
and the CPUs
are now the critical path of the most
expensive part of the data center.
This is the most expensive for a good
reason.
The
economics the economics of the AI
factory is tokens.
And the tokens are created here.
And so of course you want to manufacture
and generate as many tokens as possible.
This is where you put all of your
economics. And this has to not be in the
way.
And so Vera CPU has great pressure on
the Vera on the CPU architecture, which
is the reason why we built a brand new
architecture from the ground up. A CPU
the world has never seen before.
We call it Vera.
This is CPU
for agents.
All the CPUs of the past we built for
humans.
This CPU is built for agents.
Well, there are four things to keep in
mind.
The four takeaways.
The first takeaway
is that the instructions per clock of
Vera has to be incredibly good because
we need the latency to be short.
We need the processing time single
threaded performance not throughput
single threaded performance has to be
world class absolutely the best.
Single threaded performance which is the
reason why the IPC
the instructions per clock of Vera is so
high. It's the highest in the world. 10
instructions fetch decoded and executed
per clock.
Number one.
Number two.
The bandwidth necessary to move data in
and out for the CPU has to be utterly
world class.
The second thing is bandwidth per core.
The third is just bandwidth period. I
said earlier a gentic systems is
fundamentally disaggregated
and distributed. Disaggregated and
distributed. When computing is
disaggregated and distributed
networking becomes the problem.
Therefore, we have to move the data
around as fast as possible between the
CPU cores and between the CPU and the
storage, the CPU and the GPU.
The bandwidth around the system and
inside the CPU core has to be utterly
world-class.
Because the CPU cores are talking to
each other with extremely high
bandwidth.
They're not rented core per core per
core, they're all working together.
The cross-sectional bandwidth of Vera is
off the charts. It's the first one to be
PCI Express Gen 6.
It is also
the first one to have LPDDR5
with 1.2 terabytes per second.
Three times two to three times the
bandwidth of the highest performance
CPUs.
CPU for agents.
And this will this this market will
surely be larger than the last. And the
reason for that is because there'll be a
lot more agents than there are people
and then they'll the agents are very
impatient. So, Nvidia
Vera CPU. Thank you.
This is the most important slide really.
This is the takeaway.
The takeaway here is that this is the
application pattern.
This is the computing pattern of the
next decade.
Agents
harnesses
orchestrating large language models.
Every company will run it.
Every company will be an agent company.
Every company will have agents running
inside.
Every company will see that
agents
will need its own operating system.
Every company is asking us, "How do we
run agents
safely? How do we build agents for our
own workloads?" And so, we have the
NVIDIA agent toolkit for enterprise AI.
You've seen me build this in plain
sight.
Almost everything that NVIDIA does, as
you know, at every GTC, if you go back
and look at my GTC 5 years ago or 10
years ago, you will see today.
This you've seen me talking about for
several years now, because we've been
building for this moment.
There are four things that companies
need in order to
build agents as a service or build
agents to operate.
The first thing you need is you need
models.
Of course, large language models. The
smarter the better. The cheaper the
better. The faster the better.
The second
is you need a harness
to orchestrate the whole thing. The
third, these eight these models want to
use tools.
And these tools come with its skills.
And I showed you CUDA-X libraries, those
are going to be amazing tools for the
agents in the future.
And then lastly,
you need a runtime.
You need the operating system that holds
it all together. This is the NVIDIA
toolkit for agents.
It includes
models
that you can modify. NVIDIA's
world-class open models and I'll show
you more.
You can run agents
from anybody. You can run uh cloud code,
incredible agent. Codex, incredible
agent. You could run it inside this
harness called open shell, which will be
highly secure for your inside the
enterprise.
The shell
protects the agent, keeps it grounded in
security policies.
Privacy is protected.
Its rights and privileges are given.
Its identity is protected. And so, this
open shell is being adopted all over the
world. NVIDIA open shell is open source.
You're going to see so many companies
adopt it. Red Hat,
Canonical, Microsoft. It's going to be
adopted everywhere.
This is an important This is the
runtime. And this runtime is fully
optimized for the NVIDIA AI platform,
which is everywhere. So, you can run
open shell
in any cloud, on prem, and even on
device.
So, you have you have now tools and
libraries
that they can use.
You have models that you can modify or
use as is, or you have agents.
This be open claw,
Hermes, another incredible another
incredible
harness. These agentic harnesses can now
run on prem or for you anywhere. One of
my favorite use cases of agents
is chip designers.
It is the single most important thing
that NVIDIA does.
And so, of course, we have to partner
with Cadence
to build super agent,
a chip design super agent.
It is orchestrated by codex or cloud
code.
It has RTL and architecture diagrams or
schematics or
uh specifications as input and whatever
you need to fix.
And together we created some super
agents
that are optimized for the NVIDIA
runtime
with NeMo Tron. NVIDIA's dedicated to
build open models for the world so that
all of you, all of us, could create our
own agents.
Today, we're announcing
the NeMo Tron
3 Ultra.
Yep, our next open model and it is
smart.
The NeMo Tron models
not only give you the model,
we give you all the data that we used to
train the model and because we have a
coalition of incredible partners, you
can see all of our partners down here.
We work together, contribute data to
each other
because of all of our great
partnerships. All of this from the
model,
the training script, and the data made
all completely available to you. This is
open models at its best.
The best open model system policies in
the world.
Simple goal is so that you can take all
of it, add to it, make it even better,
make it yours.
NeMo Tron 3 Ultra
is
five times faster. It is also
30% cheaper,
completely open.
We're completely dedicated to this. This
is now NeMo Tron 3. We're currently
working on NeMo Tron 4.
So, this entire toolkit
from models,
harnesses,
tools and skills,
and runtimes is the reason why every
enterprise company in the world has the
ability now to create their own agents
just like Cadence did with their super
agents.
Microsoft and Nvidia
are going to reinvent the PC.
This is going to be the new PC.
Now, tomorrow night tomorrow night, I
think it's tomorrow night our time,
but I'm going to be with Satya. We're
going to talk a lot more about the work
that we're doing together.
Microsoft and Nvidia over the last 3
years,
it took this long to completely reinvent
how the PC's going to work so that we
could be ready for this moment.
As I mentioned earlier,
that compute pattern called the agent,
it's going to run in AI clouds.
It's going to run inside enterprises.
It is also going to run on your PC.
What's going to happen to that PC when
it has an autonomous agent?
An agent that's helping you, that
understands you.
You could talk to it. It could look at
you. You could
ask it to refile stuff,
go help you
do some research.
It could do a lot more that I'll show
you.
But the new operating system
is of course the old operating system
plus
large language models.
Large language models in a lot of ways
is the modern version of DirectX.
It has of course input and output,
understands prompts, it understands
computer vision, it can generate video,
it can generate sounds. It is the modern
extension, the intelligence extension of
the PC, of a computer.
On top of that, the application as I
mentioned before is going to be replaced
by now an agentic runtime.
And that is the modern application, an
agent.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Nvidia's
RTX Spark laptops. Now,
thank you.
I have too many things in my pocket.
Okay.
All right.
This is the most amazing chip the world
has ever built.
This
is the N1X that we built in partnership
with MediaTek. I think I saw I saw Rick
earlier. This is N1X. This is a
beautiful chip. And this is This is a a
a chip that frankly would take 33 years
to build. And the reason for that is
because 100% of Nvidia software stack
runs here.
If you want to run uh uh digital
biology, no problem. If you want to do
seismic processing, no problem. You want
astrophysics, no problem. Everything
associated with CUDA, all the physics,
all the biology, all the genomics, all
the AI, no problem. All the computer
graphics, no problem. Every single
application Nvidia has ever created and
every single application that Windows
has ever run.
Microsoft and Nvidia meticulously
optimized everything so that this
computer literally runs everything the
world has ever created plus
it now runs agents.
An incredible computer. I'm so proud of
it. Now, that computer could have a
local NeMo Tron 3 Ultra model
or NeMo Tron 3 Super model or it could
have uh Claude code or Codex or some
other model in the cloud or something on
the network and it's going to it's going
to work and do something amazing. RTX
Spark is a reinvention
of laptop.
But in fact, Microsoft and video is
reinventing all of PC. And today we're
announcing a whole new line.
Three revolutionary Windows machines
covering desktop,
laptop, and workstations. All 100%
Windows compatible, 100% CUDA, 100%
NVIDIA AI Tensor Core.
Everything that runs that you see that
runs on NVIDIA in all these different
platforms around the world runs here.
And so, we have a roadmap for this. This
is a brand new product family for us.
Every single generation of architecture,
we will have a desktop, a laptop, a
workstation, and then a desktop, a
laptop, and workstation. And the thing
that I'm just incredibly pleased,
incredibly honored,
is that 100%
of the world's PC industry has joined us
to reinvent the PC. A new line,
a new beginning. Thank you. In the case
of language models, all the English and
all the language that we have on the
internet that we trained on was from the
perspective of us. We wrote it and we're
reading it.
However, in order to create a data for
AI robotics, it has to be in the
perception, the perspective of the
robot. And most of the world's video
data is from a third person, not first
person.
And so, a gigantic systems, robotic
systems,
physical AI, the data is the hardest
problem.
You've seen us move up this ladder. We
started with teleoperations, which is
basically human demonstration. This is
no different than the big breakthrough
of reinforcement learning human
feedback.
This Then we use simulation. This is
where Omniverse comes in. This is no
different than reinforcement learning
variable verifiable rewards. Okay? And
so, we use these systems to bootstrap
the AI model, the physical AI model.
Eventually, we're able to learn
from third per- third-person,
reprojecting it into first-person.
And now, eventually, through
bootstrapping, we have a world
foundation model that can understand the
physical world from any perspective you
want. Third-person, first-person,
outside-in, inside-out, doesn't matter.
This is a big breakthrough, indeed. And
today,
we're announcing
Cosmos 3.
Cosmos 3
is the frontier of physical AI.
We are at the frontier with language
models. There's so many people working
on it. However, in physical AI, we are
absolutely the world's best. I am so
proud of the team for doing this. This
is the foundation model for all of your
work. Whenever you want to create a
robot, whenever you want to create a
factory robot or a robot that works in a
factory,
any kind of robot there in
that
involves physical world, you now have a
companion, a Cosmos 3, that can
understand and reason.
It can generate.
It can simulate in the loop. It can even
be the policy itself. It is on the top
of leaderboards all over the all over
the world. I am incredibly proud of
Cosmos, and today we're announcing
Cosmos 3. This takes data plus compute,
gives you AI.
Now that we have AI,
compute is data.
And so, use Cosmos 3, train a whole
bunch of AI models. Cosmos is such an
incredible open model system. It's
exactly the same as NeMo tron. We open
the model.
We open the data, and we even open how
we trained it, so that you could enhance
it for yourself and turn Cosmos into
your proprietary model.
Today, we're announcing AlphaMine 2.
An open model for self-driving cars.
We're working with car companies across
the world. If you look at these brands
that have signed up for the NVIDIA
Hyperion that are building NVIDIA
Hyperion cars,
this represents about 80%
of the world's cars. The manufacturers
represent 80% of the world's cars.
We are going to have a whole lot of
NVIDIA Hyperion systems that are able to
run AlphaMine or anybody else's AV
stack.
We are also connected into mobility
services. Approximately 97% of the
world's mobility services are connecting
with us so that when we deploy AlphaMine
on the Hyperion runtime
with the Halos operating system, we will
be able to connect to all of these
services across the world. The Nvidia
Isaac Groot is our humanoid robotic
stack.
Model,
data generation,
simulation,
the runs the runtime including the
operating system. This represents
Groot
platform, the Isaac Groot platform.
Every one of our systems as you can see,
the exact same pattern whether it's
agentic system for the cloud, agentic
system for the PC,
a robotic system for a self-driving car,
a robotic system for a human robot, all
the same. And of course, in every single
case,
we build everything completely.
We build everything vertically,
completely
integrated with co-design, extreme
co-design, and then we open it up for
everybody to use whichever part you
like. And whatever you want to use, we
even help you modify.
But the one thing that is missing is we
need a reference platform for robotic
systems. These robotic systems are so
complicated, so many motors, so many
sensors, so fragile, and yet we need to
have a way
to deliver these reference platforms
just like we do with PCs and DGXs and
clouds and self-driving cars. We now are
going to do it for robots. Today we're
announcing the Nvidia Isaac Groot, a
reference humanoid robot, all fully
integrated. 25 degrees of freedom on the
on each hand made by Sharpa.
31 degrees of freedom on the robot, 6
ft, 150 lb,
just like me.
The first number is shorter, than the
second number is bigger.
Otherwise, pretty close.
And and this platform runs the new Thor
and our entire software stack.
Data generation stack, data simulation
stack, the runtime, all integrated into
a robot that is designed for everyone to
use. Now, we built this for higher
education and university researchers
because for them to build this is
insanely hard to do. The computer
industry has been completely changed.
In the last 6 months, everything
changed.
Everything changed because agents were
realized and it converged with the
latest frontier models and it made
possible
the AI to now do useful work.
The computing pattern will repeat over
and over and over again. This computing
pattern of an agent that's a model, a
harness that uses tools with skills, and
runs in a runtime.
That runtime depends on whether it's in
the cloud or on prem, on a PC, or in a
robot. But the computing pattern is
exactly the same for all of them.
You will use different harnesses because
of your preference. You will use
different models because of your
preference. You will improve them for
your proprietary use. You would create
sub super agents that you can rent to
other people to help them do their work.
This agentic platform, this agentic
pattern
Nvidia has an enterprise AI toolkit.
This is a wonderful way for all of you
to engage AIs and for us, it's a
wonderful growth opportunity.
Vera Rubin is in full production.
Whereas Grace Hopper Blackwell was
created to process AI, particularly
inference,
Vera Rubin was created to run agents. It
is in full production. It is much, much
more than a GPU. It is entire
disaggregated, distributed agent
processing system.
Nvidia has really become an
infrastructure company.
Not just a GPU company, not just a
systems company, but an infrastructure
company to help you generate the maximum
revenues, the maximum profit, and to get
there as soon as possible.
The agent world
this new way of doing computing where
you build CPUs now for agents, not for
people.
CPUs for agents has its own special
requirement, and our Nvidia Vera is
revolutionary. I'm so happy about its
ramp.
The orders already is going to make it
the fastest and the most successful
product launch in our company's history.
Nvidia and Microsoft has created a whole
new line of PCs. This is a new
beginning, and of course, that exact
same agentic pattern that I agentic
processing pattern, computing pattern
that I just described is also going to
run on all kinds of devices. I mentioned
PCs,
but in the future, it'll be robots and
satellites and base stations and
factories, in the cloud, on prem, at the
edge. This pattern, agentic AI system,
this agentic computing pattern will be
replicated in computers all over. How we
think about the personal computer will
very likely change.
I want to thank all of you for your
partnership, your friendship. We
couldn't be here without everything that
we do together. I am so proud of how
you've been so successful this last
year.
The next year
is going to be even more.
>> Very optimistic.
Stanford
recommend you to watch it.